<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/articles</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/articles"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2015-05-06T00:54:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Day Twenty-Two</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/articles/2015/05/06/day22.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/articles/2015/05/06/day22.html</id>
    <published>2015-05-06T00:54:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-05-06T01:07:23-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;// Buttons
%button.clean
  %i.fa.fa-long-arrow-left
  = link_to 'Previous', prev_page
%button.clean
  = link_to 'Next', next_page
  %i.fa.fa-long-arrow-right
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I styled the next and previous buttons at the bottom of the page. I also added Font Awesome for icons. I need to find out if there's a way to inject HAML into Markdown. If there's not, I may need to start writing these article pages in HAML.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Day Twenty One</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/articles/2015/05/05/day21.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/articles/2015/05/05/day21.html</id>
    <published>2015-05-04T23:35:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-05-04T23:50:45-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today my awesome coworker &lt;a href="http://cronfu.com/"&gt;Jimmy Thai&lt;/a&gt; helped me get to the bottom of my Heroku issue. One major reason for the errors was that I had forgotten to add _  before some of my partial Sass files. That was making the code run twice and was causing an undefined variable error. Noted!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He also explained that Heroku wasn't really the best home for a static site like this. So, we moved my site over to Github pages.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Day Twenty</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/articles/2015/05/05/day20.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/articles/2015/05/05/day20.html</id>
    <published>2015-05-04T23:35:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-05-04T23:40:54-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I forgot to add this blog post on Saturday…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I added a header and started styling the nav and footers. Not much style, but I started thinking about things and getting stuff organized. I also better organized my CSS. For some reason it appears that when I merged my day-20 branch in Github, it reverted some of my changes. Weird. Adding them back in now. I need to figure out what happened with that…&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Day Nineteen</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/articles/2015/05/02/day19.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/articles/2015/05/02/day19.html</id>
    <published>2015-05-02T08:50:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-05-04T17:18:36-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Yes! ERB to HAML complete! It's amazing how one little misplaced comma or wrong indentation can ruin it all. Aaaaand, I also learned… when in doubt, bounce dat server!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Day Eighteen</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/articles/2015/05/01/day18.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/articles/2015/05/01/day18.html</id>
    <published>2015-05-01T00:10:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-05-02T09:08:25-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welp, Danilo helped me figure out what was causing the error with my footer conversion from ERB to HAML: a comma. One measly comma. But honestly, I was pretty damn proud of myself that I got that close on my own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AND THEN… emboldened by my near success, I took on the layout.erb file and tried to convert it to HAML. Stuck again! This time, when I consulted the converter and copied and pasted in that code, it still didn't work! Grrrr. To be continued…&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Day Seventeen</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/articles/2015/04/30/day17.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/articles/2015/04/30/day17.html</id>
    <published>2015-04-30T00:02:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-04-30T00:10:15-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today I tried to convert some footer code from Ruby to HAML. I got so so close. But still no cigar. I'll figure it out soon. I'm actually really proud of myself for getting this far. I didn't use a converter or anything! I read the HAML docs and tried to figure it out on my own. 90% there… (I did try a converter after I kept getting an error 100 times trying different things, but it didn't really tell me anything I hadn't already figured out.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday my coworker Jimmy helped me understand Ruby a little better. He also helped me understand why my nested layouts weren't working: it WAS working, just not on the page I was expecting it to work on. Derp.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
